linkbynet.com 2018-09-11

# PRIVACY POLICY - LINKBYNET

The purpose of this “Privacy Policy” is to inform all individuals from whom personal data is collected by Linkbynet how Linkbynet collects and uses such personal data and how you can control its use.

This Privacy Policy sets forth the principles and guidelines governing the protection of your personal data including the personal data collected on or through the Sites.

Linkbynet collects personal Data either online (including via email) or offline and this Privacy Policy is applicable regardless of the means of collection or processing.

This Privacy Policy applies in particular to the following websites and blogs :

  * blog.linkbynet.com
  * blog.linkbynet.ca
  * rse.linkbynet.com
  * extranet.linkbynet.com
  * jobs.linkbynet.com
  * <http://thewatchmakers.fr/>
  * shakeit2017.fr

(hereinafter collectivelly the « Sites »)

**COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION DATA AND USE**

We collect certain personal information such as your name, home address, phone numbers that you may provide us by filling out forms to receive information, submit your questions, register to our services or submit a resume for a job position. The collected information may be used to contact you directly concerning your requests or to consider your application during the hiring process.

We may also collect information related to website visits through cookies. This data may be used to analyze trends, manage the website, analyze user activity and/or collect demographic information about our website visitors. Cookies can only identify you by number; information regarding your name, address or all other information that may identify you cannot be collected.

At any time, you can change your browser preferences to disable cookies or to accept them.

Xxwa

**LINKS TO WEBSITES NOT CONTROLLED BY LINKBYNET OR ITS AFFILIATES**

The Sites might offer links to third party websites which may be of interest to you.

Linbynet does not exercise any control over the content of third party websites or the practices of these third parties in connection with the protection of Personal Data that they might collect and are thus not in the control of Linkbynet. Consequently, Linbynet declines all liability for the content of third party websites or the practices of these third parties concerning the protection of personal data.

It is therefore your responsibility to inform yourself of the privacy policies of these third parties.

**TRANSFER OF PERSONAL DATA**

If you are accessing the Sites from a location outside of the European Union, with laws or regulations governing data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from those of the European Union, please note that through your continued use of the Sites, which are governed by French law, you are transferring your personal data to the European Union and you consent to that transfer.

Your personal data may be disclosed to and used by an affiliate of Linkbynet (“Linkbynet Affiliates”).

Please note that Linkbynet may transfer your personal data outside of the European Union, as long as before transferring your personal data, Linkbynet has ascertained that non European Union entities, including Linkbynet’s Affiliates, offer an adequate level of protection in accordance with European legislation.

Where Linkbynet has knowledge that a third party to which Linkbynet has provided personal data is using or disclosing personal data contrary to this Privacy Policy or to applicable laws, Linkbynet will take reasonable steps to prevent or stop such use or disclosure.

You will have the opportunity to decide whether you authorize Linkbynet to use your personal data for a purpose which is different than the purpose for which it was originally collected.

Linkbynet will also disclose your personal data to third parties if Linkbynet determines that such disclosure is necessary for technical reasons (such as hosting services by a third party) or to protect Linkbynet’s legal interests (such as in the event of a sale of assets to a third company, or a change of control or a total or partial liquidation of Linkbynet).

Additionally, Linkbynet may share your personal data with the reseller assigned to you or in the territory where You are located for the purpose of Liknbynet business. Linkbynet may also share your personal data with business partners when Linkbynet and the business partner sponsor an event together or participate in a marketing promotion together and in which you engage.

Linkbynet may also disclose your personal data if required by law or if Linkbynet believes in good faith that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process (for example, a warrant, a subpoena, or other court order) or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Linkbynet, our customers, or the public.

If allowed by applicable law, Linkbynet may also share your personal data with third parties in order to offer you targeted marketing or advertising.

These transfers may be transmitted over the internet or by any other method which Linkbynet determines is appropriate and in accordance with applicable law.

### RIGHT OF ACCESS TO AND RECTIFICATION OF THE DATA

Linkbynet will take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal data collected is used for the purposes stated in this Privacy Policy and that such personal data is correct and up to date.

You have a right to access your personal data. In addition, you have a right to request the rectification, completion, update or erasure of your personal data. You also have a right to obtain a copy of the personal data stored by Linkbynet.

If you have an account, you can exercise your rights of access to and rectification of the personal data by logging on to your account. Otherwise, you may exercise your rights of access to and rectification of the data by sending an email to the following address: [dataprotection@linkbynet.com](mailto:dataprotection@linkbynet.com)

**DATA SECURITY AND RECIPIENTS**

Linkbynet undertakes to ensure the protection and security of personal data that you choose to communicate, in order to ensure the confidentiality of your personal data and prevent your personal data from being distorted, damaged, destroyed or disclosed to unauthorized parties.

Linkbynet maintains reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal data from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alternation and destruction.  As part of those safeguards, Linkbynet employs sophisticated technology designed to protect personal data during its transmission and prevent transmission errors or unauthorized acts of third parties.  However, while Linkbynet strives to protect your personal data, in light of the inevitable risks of data transmission over the internet, Linkbynet can not guarantee full protection against any error occurring during the course of personal data transmission which is beyond Linkbynet’s reasonable control.

Since all personal data is confidential, access is limited to employees, contractors and agents of Linkbynet or Linkbynet Affiliates who have a need to know such data in carrying out their tasks. All the people who have access to your personal data are bound by a duty of confidentiality and subject to disciplinary actions and/or other sanctions if they fail to meet these obligations.

However, it is important for you to exercise caution to prevent unauthorized access to your personal data. You are responsible for the confidentiality of your password and information appearing on your account. Consequently, you must ensure that you log out of your session in the event of shared use of a computer.

**BINDING CORPORATES RULES (BCR)**

Safeguarding the privacy and security of personal information is a top priority for Linkbynet in our data driven-economy. Linkbynet has become one of the world’s first enterprise IT management provider to secure EU accreditation for its Data Privacy Binding Corporate Rules as both a Controller and Processor of personal data.

The BCR certification has been approved by the European Data Protection agencies. The approval covers both Linkbynet’s handling of personal data (Controller) as well as the personal data it handles on behalf of its customers (Processor).

The Linkbynet’s BCR Policy is incorporated into a corporate wide policy, requiring all Linkbynet entities, employees and third party providers to comply with and respect the BCR Policy which is governing the collection, use, access, storage and transfer of personal data among Linkbynet entities and third-party sub-processors worldwide.

The BCR Policy applies to all personal data of past, current and potential employees, customers, resellers, suppliers, service providers and other third parties wherever it is collected and used in conjunction with Linkbynet business activities and the administration of employment.

Linkbynet will apply the BCR Policy universally in all cases where Linkbynet processes personal data, whether the personal data relates to European individuals or not, even though EU data protection laws only apply to personal data collected in Europe.

If you have any questions regarding the provisions of the BCR Policy, your rights under the BCR Policy or any other data protection issues, you can contact Linkbynet’s Data Protection Officer at the address below (see « Contact Us ») who will either deal with the matter or forward it to the appropriate person or department within Linkbynet.

### **DISPUTE RESOLUTION**

### ** **

Although Linkbynet has put in place reasonable safeguards to protect personal data, we recognize that there is no method of transmitting or storing personal data that is completely secure.

However, Linkbynet is committed to ensure the privacy of personal data: if you have a reason to believe that the security of your personal data has been compromised or misused, you should contact Linkbynet via the following address: [dataprotection@linkbynet.com](mailto:dataprotection@linkbynet.com)

Linkbynet will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints regarding use and disclosure of personal data in accordance with the principles contained in this Privacy Policy.

Unauthorized access to personal data or the improper use of personal data may constitute offenses under local law.

**COOKIES AND LOG FILES**

As mentioned previously, Linkbynet may use cookies to collect information about its visitors. A cookie is a data file that your hard drive sends through your computer’s web browser that allows us to identify your browser. You can deactivate cookies at any time by accessing your web browser’s preferences.

Linkbynet may also use log files to collect data about its visitors. Linkbynet may review server logs for security purposes, such as detecting network intrusions. In the event of a criminal intrusion, server log data, which includes visitors’ IP addresses, may be used to trace and identify a person. In such cases, raw log data would be shared with the agencies authorized to investigate these criminal breaches

Log files and cookies do not automatically link the data you provide by visiting our website with your personal information.

**YOUNG AUDIENCE**

The Sites are not designed for children and do not intentionally target a young audience. We do not voluntarily collect or store any personal child information on our Sites. If we find that we have inadvertently received such information, we remove it from our system.

**CONSENT**

By using the Sites, you grant us the right to collect, use and disclose your personal information as described in our Privacy Policy. Linkbynet reserves the right to modify this policy at its discretion without notice.

**DURATION OF CONSERVATION OF PERSONAL DATA**

Personal data must not be stored beyond the time necessary for the purpose of the processing. The navigation data will be kept for a maximum of 6 months according to the recommendations of the CNIL.

**CONTACT US**

For any additional question concerning this Privacy Policy, to opt out of receiving information from Linkbynet or any request for rectification, completion, update, or deletion of your personal data you may send an email to the following email address:[dataprotection@linkbynet.com](mailto:dataprotection@linkbynet.com)
